{
    "subject": "resource/The_Flys_(US_band)",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The Flys (US band) are from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9573085904121399,
            "question": "Is The Flys a US band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7855230569839478,
            "question": "Where is the band The Flys from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6132846474647522,
            "question": "What country are The Flys from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5317025184631348,
            "question": "Are there any other bands similar to The Flys?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5218319892883301,
            "question": "Can you name any bands from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49793049693107605,
            "question": "Are there any famous musicians from the US?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40986543893814087,
            "question": "What type of music does The Flys play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3999080955982208,
            "question": "What nationality is The Flys?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32092440128326416,
            "question": "Has The Flys released any albums?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30973130464553833,
            "question": "Where have The Flys performed live?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Flys (US band) are from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8838_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has The Flys released any albums?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8838_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is The Flys?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8838_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of music does The Flys play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8838_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8838_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8838_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8838_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8838_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8838_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8838_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8838_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8838_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8838_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8838_54.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe document explicitly states that  \"American punk rock group The Flys has put out a number of albums and songs throughout the years.\"  This information supports the triple. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The Flys (US band) are from United States.\" Specifically, one of the documents mentions that \"The Flys, a punk rock group from Hollywood, California,\" which confirms their origin in the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n\nBased on the information provided, it is clear that The Flys is a punk rock group from Hollywood, California. Since Hollywood is in the United States, this supports the statement that The Flys (US band) are from the United States."
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The information provided states that The Flys is a Punk Rock group from Hollywood, California. This indicates that the band is based in California, United States, not the entire United States.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The Flys' formation in Coventry, England (point 3) contradicts the statement that they are from the United States.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}